A Finding Aid to the Jackson Pollock and Lee Krasner Papers, circa 1914-1984, bulk 1942-1984, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Jackson Pollock papers and Lee Krasner papers about Jackson Pollock, circa 1914-1984; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 7.4 Linear feet Box 1-7, 16, OV 18, FC 19-22
  - Writings by Others, 1950-circa 1983, undated; 1.3; Archival Resource Key
    Found here are essays, articles, lectures, and biographies about Jackson Pollock. There is an original draft of the Bryan Robertson biography of Jackson Pollock, an essay by Clement Greenberg, and an essay written by Lee Krasner after Pollock's death which discusses his career, personal life, and their relationship.
    Items are arranged alphabetically by author's last name.
    - Bruno Alfieri, "L'Arte Moderna: A Short Talk on The Pictures of Jackson Pollock,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Lance Compa, "Jackson Pollock: Art and Cosmos,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Francine du Plessix and Cleve Gray, "Who Was Jackson Pollock,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Marilyn G. Foley, "Jackson Pollock: Where the Action Is,", circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - B.H. Friedman, "Sketches for a Portrait: Jackson Pollock,", 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Robert Goodnough, "Jackson Pollock,", 1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Clement Greenberg, "Jackson Pollock,", circa 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Stanley Harrison, "Lavender Mist by Jackson Pollock: A Critique,", circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Lee Krasner, "Pollock,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Rosalind E. Krauss, Untitled Essay, circa 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Krauss/Namuth, Untitled Essay, circa 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - London Exhibition Catalog, draft copy, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - John Bernard Myers, Review of Jackson Pollock: The Last Sketchbook, circa 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Francis O'Connor, "Hans Namuth's Photographs of Jackson Pollock as Art Historical Documentation", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Francis O'Connor, "Jackson Pollock and the WPA Federal Art Project: 1935 to 1943,", 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Bryan Robertson, Jackson Pollock, draft copy, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Alvin Schwartz, Untitled Essay, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Eugene Victor Thaw, Untitled Essay, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Parker Tyler, "Jackson Pollock: The Infinite Labyrinth,", 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Unidentified Author, "Jackson Pollock,", 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - James Valliere Research Material on Jackson Pollock, 1963-1972; 1.4; Archival Resource Key
    James Valliere was a graduate student at the University of New Hampshire who was employed in 1963 by Lee Krasner to begin researching Pollock's early career and compile a general catalog of his work. Valliere never published the results of his research and the materials were kept by Lee Krasner. Found here is correspondence between Valliere and Lee Krasner, as well as Valliere's research correspondence with other family members, and Pollock's friends and colleagues. There is correspondence with Mr. and Mrs. Charles Pollock, Sanford McCoy (Pollock's brother), Jay Pollock, Thomas Hart Benton, Robert Motherwell, and the Art Students League of New York. Also found are transcripts and audio recordings of interviews conducted by Valliere with those who knew Pollock well, including James Brooks, Reuben Kadish, Tony Smith, Clement Greenberg, and Pollock's sister-in-law Mrs. Sanford (Arloie) McCoy wherein she reads several letters Jackson wrote to his father from New York. Also included in this series are some of Valliere's research notes and photographs of James Brooks, and Pollock's friend Daniel Miller taken during their interviews. Untranscribed audio recordings of interviews are filed in series 1.10: Audio and Video Recordings and Film.
    All of the sound recordings in this series have been digitized for research access.
    - Correspondence, 1963-1967; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 53-55)
    - Notes, 1963-1964, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Photographs of James Brooks, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Photographs of Daniel T. Miller, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Preliminary Catalog of Jackson Pollock's Library, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - James Brooks Interview, 1965; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Duplicate; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript Original (Box 2, Folder 60-62)
    - Clement Greenberg Interview Transcript, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Clement Greenberg Interview, 1968; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound tape reels Original (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
    - Reuben Kadish Interview, Transcript, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. Sanford McCoy Interview, 1965; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript Original (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
    - Daniel T. Miller Interview, 1965; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Duplicate; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript Original (Box 3, Folder 6-8)
    - Tony Smith Interview, Transcript, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Interview with Lee Krasner, Mr. and Mrs. Charles Maddox, Dorothy Dehner, and Robert Miller, Transcript, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Essay, "Jackson Pollock's Progressed Lunation Cycle,", 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Business Records, circa 1942-1983; 1.5; Archival Resource Key
    Business records document Lee Krasner's handling of Pollock's estate and exhibition of his artwork after his death. Found here are miscellaneous business records, including price lists, lists of items loaned for exhibitions, warehouse and shipping receipts, conservation receipts, and other handwritten notes. There are lists of owners of paintings and exhibitions, a guest book from the Venice "Biennale, and a complete appraisal of 37 Jackson Pollock drawings. There is also a folder of account statements and inventory lists from the Marlborough Gallery. Legal Documents include a deposition by Francis O'Connor regarding his interviews with Pollock's therapist, Dr. Joseph Henderson.
    - Miscellaneous Business Records, 1957-1983, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders; partially scanned) (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
    - List of Owners of Paintings, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Lists, 1942-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Guest Book, Venice "Biennale,", 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Marlborough Gallery Account with the Pollock Estate, 1969-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Legal Documents, Francis O'Connor Deposition, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Appraisal of Jackson Pollock Drawings, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Printed Material, 1942-1983; 1.6; Archival Resource Key
    Printed materials include books and book proofs, such as a small book in Italian critiquing Pollock's work and proofs for two biographies by Frank O'Hara and Bryan Robertson, magazines with feature articles on Pollock, and numerous newspaper and magazine clippings spanning forty years. Also found are exhibition catalogs, posters, press releases, announcements, and invitations for both Pollock's solo and group exhibitions.
    - Book, Masterpieces of the World (in Japanese), undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Book, Museum of Modern Art New York in Bern (in German), 1978; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Book, Pollock: un saggio critico di Enrico Crispolti, 1958; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Book Proof, Betty Parsons Gallery Catalog, 1951; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Book Proof, Edwin Miller, for the essay "The Radical Vision of Whitman and Pollock,", 1970; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Book Proof, Museum of Modern Art Jackson Pollock Exhibition Catalog, 1967; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Book Proof, Frank O'Hara, Jackson Pollock, 1959; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Book Proof, Bryan Robertson, Jackson Pollock, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Book Proofs, unidentified, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Clippings, 1943-1951, undated; Archival Resource Key; (6 folders) (Box 3, Folder 29-34)
    - Clippings, 1952-1960; Archival Resource Key; (7 folders) (Box 4, Folder 1-7)
    - Clippings, 1961-1970; Archival Resource Key; (6 folders; Oversized items in Box 16, F1) (Box 4, Folder 8-13)
    - Clippings, 1971-1983; Archival Resource Key; (6 folders) (Box 4, Folder 14-19)
    - Clippings, Beaubourg Exhibition, 1982; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders; in french) (Box 4, Folder 20-22)
    - Clippings, Reviews of Jackson Pollock by Bryan Robertson, 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Clippings, Reviews of Jackson Pollock: Energy Made Visible by B. H. Friedman, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Invitations, 1944-1964, 1974-1983, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Solo Exhibitions, 1943-1979; Archival Resource Key; (5 folders) (Box 4, Folder 27-31)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Group Exhibitions, 1942-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Group Exhibitions, 1950-1970; Archival Resource Key; (14 folders) (Box 5, Folder 1-14)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Group Exhibitions, 1971-1977; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Exhibition Posters, 1950-1980; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in OV 18) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Magazines, LIFE, 1949, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Magazines, Miscellaneous, 1958, 1963, 1967, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
    - Press Releases for Pollock Exhibitions, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1974-1983, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1967; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 4, F8-13) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition Posters, 1950-1980; Archival Resource Key; (See also Box 6, F3; not scanned) (Box OV 18)
  - Scrapbooks, 1943-1957; 1.7; Archival Resource Key
    Two scrapbooks contain newspaper clippings, magazine clippings, and exhibition announcements. One was created by Pollock and Krasner, and the other was created by Krasner in the years following Pollock's death.
    - Scrapbook, 1943-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook kept by Lee Krasner, 1956-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Artwork by Others, undated; 1.8; Archival Resource Key
    Found here is one sketchbook containing primarily ink drawings and diagrams by an unidentified artist.
    - Sketchbook by Unidentified Artist, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, circa 1914-1969; 1.9; Archival Resource Key
    Found here are extensive photographs of Pollock. There are many photographs of Pollock as a child and teenager and with his family, of Pollock with Lee Krasner in the studio, outdoors, at their home on Long Island, and with family and friends, including photographs from a 1950 Pollock family reunion held at their home. Also found are exhibition photographs, including his 1951 solo exhibition at Betty Parsons Gallery, as well as photos of Pollock's studio, and a few other miscellaneous images. Several of the photographs of Pollock in his studio were taken by Herbert Matter, Hans Namuth, and Rudy Burckhardt. Photographs taken by Herbert Matter were previously incorrectly attributed to Wilfrid Zogbaum. Significant figures photographed with Pollock include Clement Greenberg, Helen Frankenthaler, James Brooks, and David Alfaro Siqueiros. There are also numerous photographs and slides of Pollock's works of art that have not been scanned. Photographs are arranged according to subject and chronologically within each folder.
    - Portraits of Jackson Pollock, 1943-circa 1955, undated; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 16, F4) (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Portraits of Jackson Pollock by Hans Namuth, 1950; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 16, F5) (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Portraits of Jackson Pollock, Copy Prints and Negatives, 1943-circa 1955; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
    - Jackson Pollock in His Studio by Herbert Matter, 1947; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 16, F6) (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Jackson Pollock in His Studio by Rudy Burckhardt, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Jackson Pollock in His Studio by Hans Namuth, 1950; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 16, F7) (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Jackson Pollock in His Studio, Copy Prints and Negatives, circa 1947, 1950; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Jackson Pollock and Family, circa 1914-1930, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Jackson Pollock and Family, Copy Prints and Negatives, circa 1914-1930, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Jackson Pollock and Lee Krasner, circa 1946-1955; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders; Oversized items in Box 16, F8) (Box 6, Folder 20-21)
    - Jackson Pollock and Lee Krasner, Copy Prints and Negatives, circa 1946-1955; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Pollock and Krasner with Friends and Family, 1936-1956; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 23-24)
    - Pollock and Krasner with Friends and Family, Copy Prints and Negatives, 1936-1956; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Pollock Family Reunion, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Pollock Family Reunion, Copy Prints and Negatives, 1950; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Pollock-Krasner Studio by Maurice Berezov, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Exhibition, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1951; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 16, F9-11) (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Exhibition, Betty Parsons Gallery, Copy Prints and Negatives, 1951; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Exhibition, Bennington College, 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Exhibitions, Sidney Janis Gallery, 1952-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Exhibitions, Unidentified, 1958, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Exhibition, Kunstverein fur die Rheinlande und Westfalen, 1961; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 34-35)
    - Exhibition, Moderna Museet, circa 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Exhibitions, Marlborough Gallery of Art, 1964, 1969, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 37-38)
    - Exhibitions, Museum of Modern Art, 1969, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1942-1948, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, Copy Prints and Negatives, 1942-1948, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Artwork, 1969, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Slides of Artwork, 1950, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Color Transparencies of Pollock Artwork Owned by Lee Krasner, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Stereo Transparencies of Pollock-Krasner Studio, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Safety Negatives, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Portraits of Jackson Pollock, 1943-circa 1955, undated; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 6, F10) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Portraits of Jackson Pollock by Hans Namuth, 1950; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 6, F11) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Jackson Pollock in His Studio by Herbert Matter, 1947; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 6, F14) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Jackson Pollock in His Studio by Hans Namuth, 1950; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 6, F16) (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Jackson Pollock and Lee Krasner, circa 1946-1955; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders; Scanned with Box 6, F20-21) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition, Betty Parsons Gallery, 1951; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 6, F29) (Box 16, Folder 9-11)
  - Audio and Video Recordings and Film, 1964, 1966; 1.10; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains a 16 mm film about Pollock, entitled, "Jackson Pollock: A Reconsideration," including a reel of outtakes, produced in 1964 by Channel 13 WNDT, the Educational Broadcasting Corporation. There are also VHS copies of the film. Also found are untranscribed audio recordings of interviews conducted by James Valliere while he was researching Pollock's early career and artwork for a never-published book on Pollock. Interviews are with artists Willem De Kooning and Alfonso Ossorio, and Pollock's friends Burton Rouche. Researchers should also see Series 1.4: James Valliere Research Material on Jackson Pollock for additional recordings of interviews with transcripts.
    All of the sound recordings in this series have been digitized for research access. Video access copies of the films are also available.
    - "Jackson Pollock: A Reconsideration," Final, 1964; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16 mm (Item FC 19)
    - "Jackson Pollock: A Reconsideration," Outtakes, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Item FC)
      - "Jackson Pollock: A Reconsideration", Outtakes, Reel 1, 1964; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 20)
      - "Jackson Pollock: A Reconsideration", Outtakes, Reel 2, 1964; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 21)
      - "Jackson Pollock: A Reconsideration", Outtakes, Reel 4, 1964; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 35mm (Item FC 22)
      - "Jackson Pollock: A Reconsideration", Outtakes, Reel 3, 1964; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 23)
    - "Jackson Pollock: A Reconsideration", 1964; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Video is access copy for motion picture film.
    - "Jackson Pollock: A Reconsideration," Outtakes, 1964; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Scope and Contents
      File includes lab records and original envelope found with film
    - Willem De Kooning interview with James Valliere, 1966; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Alfonso Ossorio interview with James Valliere, 1966; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes Duplicates; 1 Sound tape reel Duplicate; 1 Sound tape reel Original (Box 7, Folder 8-10)
    - Ruth and Tino Nivola interview with James Valliere, 1966; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Burton Rouche interview with James Valliere, 1966; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Lee Krasner Papers, circa 1927-1984; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 8.6 Linear feet Box 7-15, 17
  This series consists primarily of papers documenting Lee Krasner's artistic career and personal life during the last twenty years of her life. The bulk of the material dates from 1964 to 1984. Biographical material documents Krasner's family background, education, and career through chronologies, awards, resumes, exhibition lists, bibliographies, address books, and mementoes from Krasner's 1965 trip to England. Professional and personal correspondence is with gallery owners, curators, art historians and critics, students, fans, family, and fellows artists such as Cleve Gray, Alfonso Ossorio, and Philip Johnson.
  There are thirteen transcripts of interviews with Krasner conducted by art historians and journalists. The interviews discuss Krasner's life and career, the art scene in New York, and her relationship with Jackson Pollock. Original audio recordings exist for many of the interviews and are filed in 2.10, Audio and Video Recordings. Writings by others consist of draft essays about Krasner and her artwork; writings by Lee Krasner consist of handwritten lecture notes and notes containing reminiscences. Business and financial records consist of loan forms, sales lists, guest lists, exhibition checklists, and other miscellaneous materials. Krasner's papers also include one scrapbook of news clippings and photographs from her 1965 Whitechapel exhibition.
  Printed material consists of exhibition materials for Krasner's solo and group shows, event announcements, programs, numerous newspaper and magazine clippings, and faculty materials for her work at the Cooper Union. Numerous photographs include photographs of Krasner with Pollock, family, and friends, and photos of her home and studio. The majority of photographs are professional portraits of Krasner taken throughout her career, including portraits by Hans Namuth. Also found are photographs of Krasner at exhibitions, exhibition installations, and photographs of her artwork. Audio and video recordings include Krasner interviews, recorded radio and television shows, lectures, and a VHS recording of "Pollock a Beaubourg. Transcripts for many of the interviews are filed in Series 2.3.
  The bulk of this series has been scanned from microfilm. All of the sound recordings in this series have also been digitized for research access.
  The Lee Krasner Papers series is arranged into 10 subseries:
  2.1: Biographical Material, circa 1927-1983
  2.2: Correspondence, circa 1941-1984
  2.3: Interview Transcripts, circa 1965-1979
  2.4: Writings by Others, circa 1965-1981
  2.5: Writings by Lee Krasner, circa 1977-1979
  2.6: Business and Financial Records, circa 1957-1983
  2.7: Scrapbook, 1965
  2.8: Printed Material, circa 1942-1984
  2.9: Photographs, circa 1929-1983
  2.10: Audio and Video Recordings, circa 1964-1983
  The arrangement is based primarily on the original microfilm arrangement.
  Missing Title
  - Biographical Material, circa 1927-1983; 2.1; Archival Resource Key
    Found here are Lee Krasner's genealogical notes, school transcripts, certificate of marriage to Jackson Pollock, and Who's Who biographies. Also included are resumes and artist statements, chronologies, exhibition lists, bibliographies, and address books. Awards and certificates include an award medal for the Chevalier de l'Ordre des Arts et des Lettres. There are also mementos such as brochures, receipts, programs, and letters, from her 1965 visit to England for the Whitechapel Gallery exhibition.
    - Biographical Documents, 1927-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Biographical Data and Chronologies, 1964-1983, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Lists, 1965-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Bibliographies, 1983, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Award Medals, 1977, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Award Ceremony Programs, 1977, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)